Shreyas Honnalli

MEng Computer Science With Artificial Intelligence

Address 16 Walmsley Road, Leeds, LS6 1NG

Phone +447484801793

E-mail honnallishreyas@gmail.com

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/shreyas-honnalli-

866a65202

An eager and mathematically talented Computer Science student ready to further develop computing and coding skills. Dedicated to working accurately and efficiently in order to apply knowledge gained throughout computer science courses to real-world challenges. Keen to learn about the methods and work culture in software engineering and to see how technology is driving the modern world, especially with application development. Have experience using C/C++, Java and Python, and also in a high energy, fast paced environment through other forms of work experience.

Education

2020-09 - Current

Master of Engineering: Computer Science And Artificial Intelligence

University of Leeds

Key module scores 1st year(All following modules were passed with 1st class)-

Procedural Programming(C language) - 77%

Object Oriented Programming (Java) - 72%

Programming for the web (Python) – 72%

2015-09 - 2020-07

A Levels And GCSEs

Lawrence Sheriff Grammar School - Warwickshire

Mathematics - A*, Further Mathematics - A, Physics - A, Economics - A
GCSEs most 9s (A* distinctions) including Maths and Further Maths. English grades 6 and
7.

Academic Projects

Year 1:

- Route Finding project- Individual Project written in C(XCode IDE) and compiled using CMake.
 Project involved Dijkstra's algorithm where given a number of nodes and data of the links between nodes, program can calculate the shortest distance between two nodes and provides you the path between the two nodes. Also draws a map of nodes using gnuplot.
- Baccarat- Individual Project written in Java (Intellij IDE). Project involved using superclasses
 CardCollection, Card and subclasses BaccaratCard(of type Card), Shoe and
 BaccaratHand(both of type CardCollection). Two hands from a shuffled shoe one for the
 player and one for the banker and the game is played as normal for as many rounds as the
 user desires.

Achievements

- Young Enterprise- Entered a business competition with 20 other people as a team in order to
 construct a detailed and developed business plan. Our team placed second in the
 competition with ten other teams looking to secure pre-seed funding from investors. Absorbing
 vital skills in financial organisation, teamwork, communication and creativity.
- Cricket- Played Premier division club cricket having represented county and district youth teams and being voted best club batsman of the year in 2017.

Technical Skills

Languages - C/C++, Java, Python. IDEs - XCode IDE , Intellij Idea. Other technical skills- Agile Methodology, SQL and databases

Key Employability Skills

Teamwork- Playing competitive cricket throughout most of my youth has led to me being very familiar with teamwork as we are a collective trying to achieve a common goal.

Computational/programming skills- All computational skills listed in my technical skills section. Problem Solving- Multiple coding projects has led to my problem solving capacity enlarging multiple-fold.

Business planning awareness- Young Enterprise has led to vigorous improvement in knowledge of how businesses operate and how they achieve their goals and profit margins.

Work History

2019-07 - 2019-07

Trainee

HSBC, Coventry, Warwickshire

- Provided user feedback of the interface of the HSBC commercial banking app to relevant management and gave pointers of improvement for user experience
- Collaborated with commercial banking team with collection and clearing of documents produced from the app

2020-06 - 2020-08

Warehouse Associate

DHL, Rugby, Warwickshire

- Inspected incoming and outgoing shipments to verify accuracy and prevent errorsusing organisational planning and teamwork.
- Assembled and filled more than 100 items per hour in a high pressure environment with all correct documentation.

References

Academic Reference:

Professor B Bennett, Leeds School of Computing, b.bennett@leeds.ac.uk, Tel: 0113-34-31070